{
    "id": "dcad764e8c6c4a7b9fc2616b63a1e267",
    "title": "Most and most of: grammar exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "23b21a77490e4f078e9b36c4171b9e1b",
            "title": "Most And Most Of",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "………………… cheese is made from milk.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Most",
                        "Most of",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "………………….. England was under water.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Most",
                        "Most of",
                        "Either could be here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "………………… people like movies.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Most",
                        "Most of"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "………………… people in Switzerland can speak French.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Most",
                        "Most of",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She has eaten …………………. that cake.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "most",
                        "most of",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "She wasn’t as intelligent as her sisters, but she was …………………. beautiful.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "most",
                        "most of",
                        "the most"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "…………………. my friends are non-smokers.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Most",
                        "Most of"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "………………… . us were impressed with the plan.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Most",
                        "Most of",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Which country produces the ………………… milk?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "most",
                        "most of",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "…………………. them were uneducated.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Most",
                        "Most of",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}